There is a dissatisfaction in the Republican vote of MP Ramdas Athavale due to the appointment of the state government's college in Mahad College of People's Education Society of Babasaheb Ambedkar. The Republican Bahujan Vidyarthi Parishad has protested against the government's decision and the state government will have to face its protest. People from Pune's Education Society founded by Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar, are from Mahad, Pune, Aurangabad, Marathwada, Konkan and many places in Bangalore. No government has shown the courage to take action till now by Babasaheb Ambedkar. In the Babasaheb Ambedkar College for several days, there was a dispute between the principal.
Aam Aadmi Party's rebel leader, Shanti Bhushan, has criticized Kejriwal for betraying Anna Hazare's betrayal by Kejriwal by taking a false step in the fodder scam of Kejriwal-Lalu. However, Shanti Bhushan criticized Kejriwal for being forgetful about the dream that Kejriwal has forgotten his dream, and said that Kejriwal is a dictator. Shanti Bhushan alleged that Kejriwal had shown the same to Laloo Prasad Yadav, the accused in the fodder scam during Nitish Kumar's swearing-in ceremony. Bhushan, one of the founding members of the country's former law minister and its founder, has alleged that Kejriwal is acting as a Khap Panchayat. However, Lalu Yadav, former Bihar chief minister, took Kejriwal's coercion and forced Kejriwal to hug Laloo in the absence of political motivation.
It will take time to get good days - LK Advani 'After the Bihar elections, there is a consciousness in the party. However, BJP's senior leader LK Advani said today that it will take time to come to a good day. They had come to vote in the local elections in Ahmedabad, Gujarat. I believe it takes time to make changes in the system. Polling is going on for six municipal corporations in Gujarat today.
Pak violates ceasefire once again In Poonch district of Jammu, Pakistani troops once again violated the Armed Forces by firing on the Line of Control (LoC) Indian posts. Srinagar: Pakistani troops once again violated arms and ammunition in Poonch district of Jammu by firing at Indian positions on Line of Control (LoC). On Saturday night, they started fierce firing. Indian troops also responded to the firing by launching Pakistani troops in the Indian posts of Shahapur sector of Poonch district. The firing started from the Pakistani army till four o'clock in the morning. No Indian soldier was injured in the firing, military officials said.
If the Sangh's role is to break Maharashtra, then they must first defeat Gujarat: Raj Thakrek. MNS president Raj Thackeray has warned that the state's former Advocate General, Shreehi Aane, will be remembered for his birthday throughout the year. Nagpur's former Advocate General, ShriHari Anse, got the cake of Independent Vidarbha. The cake was cut for the birthday. Because of continuous injustice to Vidarbha and Marathwada, Shri Lahiri took the role of separate Vidarbha and Marathwada. Congress leader Nitesh Ranee took responsibility.